Inder Pal Singh

Sahibzada Ajit Singh Nagar, Punjab, India



ips17009@gmail.com



(+91) 8591773009



linkedin.com/in/ips17009

Summary

Full stack developer with 7+ years of experience.(PHP || Node || Angular || React || Next.js || Python || AWS || Docker || Cloud || MySQL || MongoDB || RDS || API || Security || React Native || Laravel || Wordpress || Magento || Bigcommerce || Codeigniter || || Google API's || 3rd Party Integrations || Paypal || Authorize.net || Web Services || HTML || JS) and completed 300+ projects.

Experience

illuminz Full Stack Engineer

illuminz

Jun 2018 - May 2021 (3 years)

Defisioff Senior Software Engineer

Deftsoft

Jan 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 5 months)

Senior Web Developer

Webclouds Technologies

Oct 2013 - Dec 2016 (3 years 3 months)

I worked as a team leader and completed more than 200+ projects in various technologies (PHP, Wordpress, Magento, Drupal, Opencart, Ontraport, CS Cart)

Education



Kalinga University, Raipur

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology 2014 - 2016



Punjab infotech

DIT, Information Technology 2012 - 2013



+2, Non Medical 2011 - 2012

Skills

PHP • React.js • Angular • Node.js • Python (Programming Language) • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • MySQL • MongoDB • Docker Products

Honors & Awards



Employee of year - Webclouds

Jan 2017